wuapi.com 2009-05-01

# Wuapi: your life in high definition

Wuapi applies measures to guarantee its Users’ privacy. When Wuapi’s services are used, we receive and compile different types of personal information. 

  * Wuapi compiles personal information (“Personal information” is the information you provide us when you register and create an account with Wuapi and that identifies you personally such as your name, e-mail address or other types of data, such as a password to be used to protect your account against non-authorised access).
  * Wuapi’s servers save information automatically when you visit our website or use our products, including the URL, IP address, type of browser and language, and the date and time of your request. Likewise, we use the personal information to identify users and some data that does not allow personal identification (such as information on the use of anonymous users, cookies, click monitoring information, etc.) to improve the quality, design and User services of the Wuapi sites.
  * We can use the personal information to offer the services you have requested, including services that show content and personalised advertising.
  * We can share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including in compliance with legal proceedings, to prevent fraud or imminent injury and to ensure the security of our network and services.
  * You may watch videos on Wuapi without having a Wuapi account.
  * To perform other activities on Wuapi such as uploading videos, publishing comments, bookmarking videos or watching restricted access videos, you must have a Wuapi account.
  * Any video or personal information content voluntarily revealed via the Internet shall be available to any Internet user and may be copied and used by other people.
  * You may update and amend the information in your personal profile and your e-mail preferences at any time.
  * You may refuse to provide us with personal information and/or reject cookies from your browser, although this may cause some our functions or services to not function correctly.
